<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><testsuite errors="0" failures="2" name="org.example.features.search.SearchByKeywordStoryDDT" skipped="0" tests="2" time="9.32" timestamp="2024-04-22 04:50:12"><testcase classname="org.example.features.search.SearchByKeywordStoryDDT" name="Search wiki by keyword test DDT"><failure message="&#10;Expected: a collection containing a string containing &quot;a collection containing a string containing \&quot;a collection containing a string containing \&quot;\&quot;\&quot;\&quot;\&quot;(cricket) Three wickets taken by a bowler in three consecutive balls.&quot;&#10;     but: was &quot;(cricket) Three wickets taken by a bowler in three consecutive balls.&quot;, was &quot;(ice hockey, soccer) Three goals scored by one player in a game, in ice hockey usually followed by fans throwing their hats onto the rink.&#10;After Jones' hat trick, the attendants had to pick up about 75 hats from the ice.&quot;, was &quot;(rugby) Three tries scored by one player in a game.&quot;, was &quot;(sports, by extension) Three achievements in a single game, or similar, such as three consecutive wins.&#10;A &quot;Gordie Howe hat trick&quot; comprises a goal, an assist, and a fighting major penalty.&#10;The car salesman came home with front-row seats after turning a hat trick at work.&quot;, was &quot;(baseball, ironic) The act of striking out three times in one game.&#10;Jones got a hat trick yesterday. Let's see if he can do something today.&quot;, was &quot;(by extension) Three incidents or achievements that occur together. quotations ▼&quot;, was &quot;&quot;, was &quot;&quot;, was &quot;&quot;, was &quot;(UK politics, historical) A means of securing a seat in the House of Commons by placing one's hat upon it.&quot;, was &quot;Any magic trick performed with a hat.&quot;" type="java.lang.AssertionError">
Expected: a collection containing a string containing "a collection containing a string containing \"a collection containing a string containing \"\"\"\"\"(cricket) Three wickets taken by a bowler in three consecutive balls."
     but: was "(cricket) Three wickets taken by a bowler in three consecutive balls.", was "(ice hockey, soccer) Three goals scored by one player in a game, in ice hockey usually followed by fans throwing their hats onto the rink.
After Jones' hat trick, the attendants had to pick up about 75 hats from the ice.", was "(rugby) Three tries scored by one player in a game.", was "(sports, by extension) Three achievements in a single game, or similar, such as three consecutive wins.
A "Gordie Howe hat trick" comprises a goal, an assist, and a fighting major penalty.
The car salesman came home with front-row seats after turning a hat trick at work.", was "(baseball, ironic) The act of striking out three times in one game.
Jones got a hat trick yesterday. Let's see if he can do something today.", was "(by extension) Three incidents or achievements that occur together. quotations ▼", was "", was "", was "", was "(UK politics, historical) A means of securing a seat in the House of Commons by placing one's hat upon it.", was "Any magic trick performed with a hat."</failure><system-err>
Expected: a collection containing a string containing "a collection containing a string containing \"a collection containing a string containing \"\"\"\"\"(cricket) Three wickets taken by a bowler in three consecutive balls."
     but: was "(cricket) Three wickets taken by a bowler in three consecutive balls.", was "(ice hockey, soccer) Three goals scored by one player in a game, in ice hockey usually followed by fans throwing their hats onto the rink.
After Jones' hat trick, the attendants had to pick up about 75 hats from the ice.", was "(rugby) Three tries scored by one player in a game.", was "(sports, by extension) Three achievements in a single game, or similar, such as three consecutive wins.
A "Gordie Howe hat trick" comprises a goal, an assist, and a fighting major penalty.
The car salesman came home with front-row seats after turning a hat trick at work.", was "(baseball, ironic) The act of striking out three times in one game.
Jones got a hat trick yesterday. Let's see if he can do something today.", was "(by extension) Three incidents or achievements that occur together. quotations ▼", was "", was "", was "", was "(UK politics, historical) A means of securing a seat in the House of Commons by placing one's hat upon it.", was "Any magic trick performed with a hat."&#13;
org.example.steps.serenity.EndUserSteps.should_see_definition(EndUserSteps.java:27)&#13;
org.example.features.search.SearchByKeywordStoryDDT.searchWikiByKeywordTestDDT(SearchByKeywordStoryDDT.java:41)&#13;
</system-err></testcase></testsuite>